Nora：ROBO, when you see this message, it means you've already arrived at Node 08.
Nora：ROBO、あなたがこれを見ている時には、 もうあなたはNode08にいる。
Nora：I'm sorry... I couldn't go there with you.
Nora：ごめんね……私、一緒にはいけない。
Nora：As long as you are with me, Mogura will definitely follow us there as well, no matter where we hide...
Nora：私と一緒にいたら、土竜は必ず追いかけてくる。 私たちがどこに逃げようとも……
Nora：The folks at Mogura want to dispose of you. You'll never be truly safe with them constantly chasing you.
Nora：土竜の人は、あなたを破壊しようとするはず。 それじゃあ、あなたは一生安全には暮らせない。
Nora：I, on the other hand, still have a lot of value to them. I am very certain that they won't harm me.
Nora：あの人たちにとって私はまだ利用価値があるから、 あの人たちが私を傷つけることはない。絶対に。
Nora：Therefore, I decide to stay here and use my ability as a bargaining chip to persuade them to no longer hold you responsible for what you did.
Nora：だから、私はここに残るね。 私の力を切り札に、あなたを追うのを止めるように説得する。
Nora：Ever since I created you, so many things have happened... We created music together. We talked with each other. We played games...
Nora：あなたができてから色々なことがあったね…… 一緒に作曲したり、おしゃべりしたり、ゲームしたり……
Nora：Whether it was the good or the bad, you were always there by my side.
Nora：大変なこともたくさん一緒に乗り越えた。 いつも……いつも……ROBO、あなたがそばにいてくれた
Nora：The time I spent with you... was truly some of the happiest times in my life. Thank you.
Nora：あなたと過ごした時間は……すごく楽しかった。 ありがとう、ROBO。
Nora：ROBO, you are a very special existence... Much more than just a simple A.I.
Nora：あなたは特別な存在……ただのA.I.じゃない
Nora：You have your own emotions, your own soul that was birthed from the database that is me——Nora.
Nora：あなたには自分の感情がある。魂がある。 それはね、全部私——Noraのデータベースから生まれたんだよ。
Nora：Do you remember what I told you before? The spirit, the mind, the memories... All of them are proof that a "human" once existed.
Nora：私が言ったこと覚えてる？ 精神、思想、記憶…… これらは全て、一人の「人間」が存在した証なの。
Nora：Therefore, for someone who inherited all of the above from me, you are the proof of my existence.
Nora：私が存在した証は、あなたの中に残り続ける。
Nora：So, please, go pursue "your own" freedom and dreams... If you do that, it's like you're pursuing my freedom and my dreams.
Nora：だから、「自分」の自由と夢を追い求めて…… それが私の追い求める自由と夢だから。
Nora：I have reconfigured your supreme command. From now on, protecting me is no longer your reason to live.
Nora：あなたの最高指令を設定し直すね。 これからは私を守るために生きなくていい。
Nora：I also forbid you from returning to Node 03.
Nora：二度とNode03に戻ってきたらダメ。
Nora：On behalf of me, experience more happy things. Let more people hear our music. Learn even more things...
Nora：私の代わりに、楽しいことをたくさん経験して。 私たちの音楽をもっとたくさんの人に届けて。 たくさん勉強して……
Nora：Go live a life that you've yearned for. This is something you deserve.
Nora：これからの生活を楽しんで。あなたはそう生きるべきなの。
[Platform announcement]：The train is about to depart. For passengers who haven't board the train, please proceed to take other trains. Thank you for your cooperation.
[プラットフォームベル]：まもなく列車が発車いたします。 まだ乗車していないお客様は、次の列車にご乗車ください。
Nora：.... Goodbye, ROBO_Head.
Nora：……ROBO_Head、さようなら。